Regarding Cheung Siu-chung's death inside
a village house in Wan Mei Village,
we don't know if someone forced
a sugarcane inside his mouth.
We won't rule out homicide.
We need you down at the Police station
to facilitate our investigation.
Cheung Tai-di's parentage is rather unusual.
Maybe because she's not my child.
Miss Tai-di never liked Master Chung.
She wanted him dead.
I did hate her.
Chung...
Hello, 999?
Yes, someone is unconscious in
Wan Mei Village.
Does anyone else live here?
No.
Control, send a coffin van to
No. 38 Wan Mei Village.
Chung...don't scare me...Chung!
The paramedics suspect when Cheung Siu-chung
was eating sugarcane,
scraps went inside his trachea by mistake
and caused him to suffocate.
Initially, it will be treated as a case
of a dead body found.
My brother has had epilepsy
since he was little.
But he was taking meds for it.
He hasn't had an episode in a long time.
How did you come across the victim?
It was his birthday; I bought him a cake.
When I walked in,
I found him lying on the floor
with a sugarcane is his mouth.
I didn't buy him any sugarcane.
I don't know where it came from.
Was the village house his home?
He was having problems at home
and didn't want to stay there.
I asked a friend to let him stay there.
You arranged for Chung to stay out?
We were all looking for him,
why didn't you say something?
You knew he had limited intelligence.
How could you let him live on his own?
What was your intention?
If you didn't help Chung,
he wouldn't stay out for so long
and choked on a sugarcane and
triggered his epilepsy.
If it happened at home,
we could have saved him.
He didn't have to die.
I'm sorry...
What's the use of apologizing now?
Chung is dead.
And you!
Chung is Father's son after all.
Why can't you accept him?
You made him run away from home.
You had a part in killing him.
Enough of your yelling.
Did you even care about Chung?
Of course I care about him.
I looked everywhere for him.
You're not worried about losing him.
You're worried about the inheritance.
Chung ran away because he was ashamed of you
who messed with your father-in-law.
You made a cuckold out of Chi.
And my grandson became an
illegitimate child.
Enough! Stop arguing!
It was your non-stop bickering
that drove Chung out of this house.
Where is it?
Chung's watch is gone!
You mean the watch Chung was wearing?
Where is it?
When the paramedics were trying to
revive Chung,
the watchband broke
and it fell to the ground
I picked it up and put it in my pocket.
But now it's gone.
I gave him that watch on his 18th birthday.
It was of great sentimental value.
You must find it.
Looks like it's gone...
Chung is dead. Even the watch is gone...
What's with the racket?
Chi...
Wait!
Chung is my son. I'll tell him.
Are we disturbing you?
Let's go upstairs...
Snail, Chung B can't play with us anymore.
Hurry up...don't look back!
Hurry! Mine is faster than yours...
Hurry!
Yours is too slow...
Like Grandpa, he's a star in the sky.
Get up! The school bus is leaving...
Happy birthday...Mom!
It's so pretty...
It took me a long time to draw...
That's very sweet of you...
We'll never...see Chung B again.
Papa missed you...
Chi, stop crying! Don't be so sad.
He's not even your son.
The body found in Wan Mei Village
may be classified as murder.
It's assigned to us.
The victim was Cheung Siu-chung.
In the autopsy report, the medical examiner
estimated his time of death
to be between 11p.m. on the 15th and
1a.m. on the 16th of this month.
We don't know if the sugarcane was
forced inside his mouth.
The clothing fiber found on the sugarcane
did not match the victim's.
It may belong to someone else.
We won't rule out homicide.
Folks from I.T. unlocked his phone.
According to the phone log and
text messages,
Cheung Siu-chung only contacted
his sister Cheung Tai-di
and a lawyer called Mok Kai-wing
in the last few days.
Let me introduce myself,
I'm Mok Kai-wing, a lawyer.
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung authorized me
to set up a trust fund to manage his assets.
I would like to read out the contents.
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung wished to leave
a 3-storey duplex in Ko Cho Village
to Ms. Leung Yuet-ping
with a proviso that
Ms. Tang Suk-han and Mr. Cheung Wang-chi
have both passed away
before Ms. Leung Yuet-ping can sell
or rent out the duplex.
The remaining $70M assets,
will be used to maintain a balanced
investment portfolio,
the profits of which will take care
of members of the Cheung family
and given to each member
in a monthly allowance
in the following amount
in Hong Kong dollars.
Ms. Tang Suk-han $50K,
Ms. Leung Yuet-ping $50K,
and Mr. Cheung Wang Chi $30K
until they pass away.
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung already signed on it.
Hold on!
Chung doesn't know anything
about wealth management.
How did he know about trust funds?
Did someone teach him?
How did he know to contact you?
Mr. Cheung contacted me personally.
As to why he wanted to set up a trust fund,
I don't exactly know.
Why don't I finish reading the document?
Kin-kwok left us this house.
Why would Chung give it to that woman?
As Mr. Cheung Siu-chung's counsel,
I'm only carrying out my client's wishes.
It doesn't make sense.
I'd like to point out one thing.
Whether Mr. Cheung Siu-chung's time of death
was before or after midnight,
is crucial to the asset allocation.
If he died on or after midnight
on October 16,
he would have been 21 years old
and was entitled to inherit
Mr. Cheung Kin-kwok's estate.
The assets will be allocated according to
the trust fund set up by him.
What if it was before midnight?
If the time of death was before
midnight on October 15,
he was not yet 21 years old.
Then he was not entitled to inherit
Mr. Cheung Kin-kwok's estate.
According to the Intestates'
Estates Ordinance,
50% will go to the spouse
and the remaining 50% will be equally
distributed among his children.
The actual time of death is still pending
the autopsy report.
I also wish to point out,
prior to Mr. Cheung Siu-chung's accident,
he contacted me
and indicated he wished to amend the
provisions of the trust fund.
My office has sent out the revised document
but unfortunately, before we received
any response from him,
Mr. Cheung passed away.
Madam Han, the Police is here.
I'm Senior Police Constable Sze King
of the Crime Unit in New Territories East.
Police Constable Cheung Yau-ming.
What is it?
Regarding Cheung Siu-chung's death inside
a village house in Wan Mei Village,
the medical examiner finished
the autopsy report.
We won't rule out homicide.
We need you down at the Police station
to facilitate our investigation.
Ms. Law Suet-chau, on the night
Cheung Siu-chung died,
the night of October 15
and after midnight on October 16,
where were you?
That night...like always,
after we finished dinner,
we went back to our rooms.
I finished doing the dishes
and went to sleep in my room.
After 12 o'clock,
I heard about Master Chung.
Between the night of the 15th
and after midnight on the 16th,
you and your husband Cheung Wang-chi
were home the whole time?
Chi goes to bed around 9 o'clock.
That's the time we usually turn in.
Your father-in-law left everything
to Cheung Siu-chung,
was your mother-in-law very upset?
Yes, we have been arguing about this.
It was Father's wishes
but Mother couldn't accept it.
She thought I persuaded Father
to leave everything to Chung.
She took out her frustration on Chung
and made him run away from home.
Was there any other reasons?
I couldn't think of any.
Cheung Siu-chung went missing for so long,
you were not worried at all?
Of course I was. But I couldn't find him.
Besides, he told me he was safe.
What did he tell you?
(2 days after Chung left)
He left a voice message
and said he needed time to think.
So I decided to give him space.
The night Cheung Siu-chung died,
where were you?
I was in bed by 10 o'clock.
Your husband left everything
to your grandson.
How do you feel about that?
I felt it was unfair for my son.
You were angry with Cheung Siu-chung
over the money?
Not exactly! It was Tai-di's fault.
She never cared about what went on at home.
But she seemed awfully helpful
and found Chung a place to stay.
I bet she wanted to coax her brother
into splitting the money with her.
Cheung Tai-di, do you know why
Cheung Siu-chung ran away from home?
Money.
Grandpa left him everything.
Grandma and Mom didn't get anything.
Chung was caught in between.
When did you arrive at the village house
in Wan Mei Village
to find Cheung Siu-chung?
I went drinking with friends.
It was around midnight when I left.
I went straight to the village house.
But I wasn't sure of the exact time.
Everyone claimed they had an alibi.
But judging from the video,
they all seemed to be hiding something.
Especially Cheung Tai-di.
As a lawyer she's prudent
and chose her words carefully.
My instincts tell me something is not right.
She was the first person at the scene
and called it in.
She also hid her brother from the family.
Too bad the village house had no CCTV.
We didn't know who was there.
What did Cheung Tai-di say
about Cheung Siu-chung
running away from home?
I was going home that day...
and saw Chung bolted out of the house
looking agitated.
I was worried about him
and followed him to the pier.
Chung, what is it?
Sis...I'm so unhappy.
I'm confused. I don't want to go home.
Why don't I find you a place to stay
for a few days?
So you can calm down, OK?
In other words, you told Cheung Siu-chung
to leave home?
You can say that.
According to Leung Yuet-ping,
Cheung Siu-chung had a smart watch
that recorded his heartbeat.
It went missing.
We asked the paramedics
and they said you picked it up.
Yes, but somehow it fell out.
Did you persuade Cheung Siu-chung
to set up the trust fund?
I only wanted to help him solve the problem.
(The day Chung ran away from home)
Sis, Grandma is mad at me.
I felt bad Mom lied to her for so long.
I want to give her some money.
But if Mom found out, she'd be upset.
What do you think I should do?
You can set up a trust fund.
Leave the house to Mom,
but on the condition that only after
Grandma and Dad have passed away,
before she'll get sole ownership.
For the rest of the assets,
share them with Grandma, Mom and Dad
as a monthly allowance.
You must state everything clearly
so they won't have cause to argue again.
And we can still live together?
Yes! If anything should happen,
I can help you deal with it
And you won't have to worry.
I must give you something.
Definitely not! I have a job.
I can make money.
Don't let them know or they'll nag.
You'll have no peace.
You're so brilliant.
The lawyer Mok Kai-wing who set up
the trust fund is your friend?
Yes! Chung wanted me to handle it.
But I don't want to get involved.
There's a conflict of interests.
So I introduced him to a friend.
You were there when the trust fund
was drafted?
That's correct.
Your Grandfather didn't leave you anything?
You're OK with that?
Grandpa was known for his
male preference mentality.
It was like that for over 20 years.
I'd be shocked if he left me anything.
Cheung Kin-kwok gave $100M to
Cheung Siu-chung.
Everyone, including Cheung Tai-di
didn't get a dime.
Would anyone be so broadminded?
There's something unusual about
Cheung Tai-di's parentage.
How was Cheung Tai-di's relationship
with Cheung Siu-chung?
Chung was nice to everybody.
Tai-di is rather indifferent
and doesn't get involved.
Maybe because she's not my child.
Before I married into this family,
Chi had a sexual relationship with
a resident at the DAC,
Tai-di's mother is also mentally challenged.
I'm not sure if my mother-in-law
wanted to save face
or didn't want to look after another
mentally challenged person.
She refused to let that woman marry
into the family.
She only took in the baby.
Tai-di grew up without her mother.
Maybe that's why she has a chip
on her shoulder.
Chau raised Tai-di.
Maybe she doesn't think we care about her.
She's wears a scowl on her face
and ignores us.
Because she grew up without her mother?
That's possible.
I know she hates me the most.
But I don't care. Let her hate me.
Grandma was the reason I couldn't see my
biological mother.
I did hate her.
Tai-di, you're home.
Father and I had business in Kowloon.
Chung will go to the tutor after
he gets out of school.
Don't just focus on your own stuff.
Make sure you watch over him, OK?
I will.
Let's go.
Tai-di, have you seen Grandpa?
No.
What about your Mom?
I don't know.
According to the helper, Auntie Chau,
Cheung Tai-di had a scary dark side
even when she was little.
She could fool others, but not me.
She never liked Master Chung
and wanted him dead.
I hate you...
What are you doing?
Chung, don't worry! I'll save you!
What a klutz!
Miss Tai-di's kindness towards Master Chung
is just an act.
Did you tell anyone about this?
No, I feel sorry for Miss Tai-di.
Besides, I raised her
and have feelings towards her.
I don't want her to get kicked out.
Leung Yuet-ping mentioned
Cheung Tai-di wanted to study abroad
and needed a lot of money.
Cheung Siu-chung wouldn't listen to her,
they argued and she killed him?
The medical examiner said
Cheung Siu-chung's time of death
should between 11p.m. on October 15 and
1a.m. on October 16.
Cheung Tai-di claimed between 10:30p.m.
and midnight on October 15,
she was drinking with friends at a bar.
We can ask her friends and
check the CCTV at the bar
and we'll know if she was lying.
Ask the fruit stands in Ko Cho Village
to see if the Cheungs or anyone else
bought any sugarcanes.
Or the sugarcane could be bought
from elsewhere.
Try to find out as much as we can.
Right!
Mom! Honey!
Good boy!
When you gave your statements,
did you shoot off your mouth
to the Police?
Don't wash your dirty laundry in public.
Kin-kwok was well respected in the village.
If word got out, we'd be humiliated.
I only answered what the Police asked me.
I didn't say anything about Master Kwok.
The instigator should keep her mouth shut.
This is nothing to be proud of.
You're the instigator.
I haven't said anything.
But you practically ignored Tai-di.
I'm not sure if she said anything.
Have some tea, Madam Han.
Judging from the officers' reaction,
I don't think they know anything.
The officer told me just now,
Chung almost drowned when he was little.
Tai-di tried to kill him out of jealousy.
What?
I also didn't expect Tai-di would
persuade Chung to give her $2M.
That's why I told the Police
Tai-di wanted to study abroad
and needed a lot of money.
How did you know about that?
Chung asked me for his red packet money.
I asked him why he needed it.
He told me he wanted to give it to Tai-di
so she could study abroad.
See? She's still held up at the
Police station.
They must have found something suspicious.
You're not pleased because
you were left out of the trust fund.
That's why you persuaded Cheung Siu-chung
to amend it, add a new clause
and give you $2M.
I only know about the original trust fund.
I didn't know there was a revision
or Chung wanted to give me $2M.
Yes, I'm friends with Mr. Mok,
but on account of confidentiality
between lawyers,
he didn't tell me anything.
The night he died,
Cheung Siu-chung texted you.
"Sis, I won't listen to you anymore."
"It's my money, I'll decide
what to do with it".
You have read it.
(The night of the incident)
I finished drinking with my friends
and I remembered it was Chung's birthday.
I bought a cake and went to
the village house.
But there was no answer.
So I took out my phone to call him.
That was when I saw the message.
Sis, I won't listen to you anymore.
It's my money, I'll decide
what to do with it.
He's so pig-headed.
That's only your version.
The truth is he decided not to
give you any money,
and texted you.
You were unresolved
and wanted to convince him under
the pretext of celebrating his birthday.
I only want $2M...
You couldn't reach an agreement
and started to argue...
Don't yell at me, Sis!
I'm not your sister.
We have different mothers.
I only want $2M...
Because Cheung Siu-chung refused
to listen to you,
you became unhinged and killed him
by mistake.
On the unpeeled part of the sugarcane,
we found fingerprints that
didn't belong to Cheung Siu-chung.
Fingerprint recognition confirmed
they belonged to you.
Chung...
I removed the sugarcane in his mouth.
Of course it had my fingerprints on it.
According to the text messages,
Cheung Siu-chung texted Mr. Mok
he received the revised document.
But we couldn't find it at the scene.
Because he wouldn't listen to you,
you killed him in a fit of anger
and took the document with you.
This is merely your speculation.
You have no proof.
Sis...
Chung?
You're off work?
What are you doing here?
Look at that big black cloud in the sky.
It's going to rain soon.
Right! Let's hurry home.
Before it starts to rain, let's go...
See? Told you. Am I brilliant or what?
Yes! Why didn't you open the umbrella?
Right!
Hurry up, brat!
It's open...
Good!
Tai-di...
Dad, what are you doing here?
Hurry home!
If you get wet,
they'll scold me for making you sick.
No, they won't...it's raining.
Chung B would have been here
if he was still alive.
He loved you very much.
Sis, you haven't eaten all night.
I'll tell you a joke,
if you think it's funny,
you must finish the noodles.
Rice noodles said, don't think I won't
recognize you after you ionized your hair.
Is that right?
That's an old joke.
But you're laughing.
You laughed, you must eat.
Come on, Sis!
Very well...It's delicious...
Come on, let's go.
Aren't we going home, Dad?
Dad...
I don't like the things they said
about you...
What is it this time?
I'm going home if you won't tell me.
OK...I'll tell you.
They said you saw Chung B drowning
but didn't save him.
You wanted him dead.
You wouldn't...you loved Chung B.
Stop!
I'll carry that.
OK!
Chung B, you're home!
Dad!
Your shoulders are wet.
You wanted to cover Chung B.
That's why I gave Chung B a big umbrella
so he could keep you dry.
You won't get your head wet
and be stupid like me.
Dad...how silly of you!
Chung too!
Chung was really good to me.
It was my fault.
Why do you say that?
Don't cry...
Well, Dad? Want another toast?
Morning, Madam Han.
Don't eat that, it's burnt. Eat this one.
Why?
I heard you coughing.
The burnt toast will give you
internal heat, right?
Since when have you become close?
Chung is gone. I want to take
better care of Dad.
Tai-di...
Can you put on butter for me?
Sure! You want condensed milk?
A toast with butter and condensed milk?
Sure!
You never know what some
people are thinking.
The better they treat you,
the more they want to hurt you.
Stay away from people like that.
What?
Time to go to the DAC.
Mom, bye, I'm going.
Don't be upset.
I'm not.
When I pick you up, I'll buy you candy.
No need.
You're so clumsy. Are you OK?
I'm fine. It wasn't my fault.
OK...
Trash should go in the trash can.
Maybe people think the box is new,
leaving it out, people make take it.
Mom said new things should be recycled.
I remember Mom threw
her favorite jacket in the trash can.
I asked her why she threw away
something so new.
She took it back.
When was this?
The day after Chung B died.
Which jacket?
Her favorite...with woolen fringes.
You have no business in the village office.
You don't need to come in anymore.
Stay home and wait on Chi.
Don't count on Chau to do it.
You're the wife.
Fine!
Auntie Chu!
Yes?
Get some oranges from Wong Kee
for ancestral worship.
The owner went back to his hometown.
It's closed.
When you went there last week,
the owner already told you...
Sh...shut up!
The Police was looking for the owner
of Wong Kee.
I told them he won't be back
for another two days.
I wonder what they want with him.
Did the owner break the law?
I don't know. Maybe it was a routine check.
Mother went to the fruit stand last week.
Why didn't she want Brother Nam
to mention it?
Did she go there to buy sugarcane?
The day after Chung died,
why did she throw away her jacket?
The one with woolen fringes.
She was wearing that when
she identified the body.
Did she go to the village house that night?
She brought it back. Where is it?
Brother Nam!
Are you going back to the shop?
Yes!
Can I hitch a ride to Kowloon?
Get in.
Where are you going?
Nanking Street.
Nanking Street...
You like driving this car?
Kin-kwok bought a new car
and gave it to me in less than six months.
It's great.
Father was kind to you.
When you started a paper product shop
a couple of years ago,
he only collected a token rent from you.
If you need to open one of similar size
the rent should be quite expensive.
I have been a good help to Kin-kwok.
And I have a tight trap.
Nobody knew about you two
these past few years.
One should know when to shut up
and when to start talking.
What do you want to know?
The night Chung died,
did you see Mother buying sugarcane
from Wong Kee?
Why didn't you tell the Police?
The Police said Chung was murdered.
He choked on sugarcane.
I need to know if Mother was involved.
Cousin Han always doted on Chung.
Even if she was angry with him,
she wouldn't kill him.
You're overthinking.
Let me get this.
What?
Nam, don't shoot off your mouth.
Don't tell anyone anything about us.
You're in trouble if anything
should happen to me.
I know. Don't be a nag.
Your mother-in-law is my cousin.
But Chung is my godson.
If anyone hurt him, I won't keep
my mouth shut.
Honey...
What?
Is my drawing pretty?
I told you to stay away from Tai-di.
She hid Chung in a village house
for a reason.
Tai-di hated Chung since she was little.
She wanted him dead.
No...that's not what happened.
Tai-di, are you OK?
Auntie Chau said the fever from a flu
may cause meningitis and make me stupid.
Then I could play with you and Chung B.
I sat in the river for a long time,
now I feel feverish.
Have I become stupid now?
Why did you do it, silly?
Dad, when I was in the river,
I already had a fever.
Chung tried to pull me up,
but I was groggy and weak.
I didn't know Chung was drowning.
Auntie Chau got the wrong idea
and thought I pushed hm in the water.
That's not what happened...
I didn't...I didn't let him drown...
Tai-di really loved Chung B...
Is it possible Tai-di was not
jealous of Chung?
Chung willingly wanted to give her $2M?
Mok Kai-wing confirmed
it was Cheung Siu-chung's idea
to revise the trust fund
and give $2M to Cheung Tai-di.
He gave specific instructions
not to disclose anything.
Cheung Tai-di knew nothing about it.
Cheug Tai-di maybe jealous of
her brother when she was little.
But it doesn't mean they can't be close
when they grew up.
I checked the CCTV and asked her friends.
She was out drinking that night.
She wasn't lying.
Tang Suk-han and Leung Yuet-ping
don't get along.
Leung Yuet-ping didn't particularly dote
on her son.
The odd thing was after Cheung Kin-kwok died
Tang Suk-han seemed to hate
Cheung Siu-chung.
Other than the inheritance,
could there be other reasons?
Cheung Siu-chung's smart watch,
could have told us his time of death.
Too bad we couldn't find it.
Hello? Yes, speaking.
You're sure about October 15?
OK, thank you.
The owner of the fruit store
in Ko Cho Village is back from China.
He said the night Cheung Siu-chung died,
Tang Suk-han bought sugarcane from him.
Sze Sir, this lady wants to see you.
Thank you.
Sze Sir, Cheung Sir, I wish to add
something to my statement.
Go ahead.
My husband told me inadvertently that
on the day after Chung died,
my mother-in-law threw away her jacket.
If she didn't have anything to hide,
why would she do that?
Was the jacket related to the case?
The night Chung died,
my mother-in-law wore it
to identify the body.
Are you suggesting Tang Suk-han
went to the village house that night,
but didn't want anyone to know,
so she threw out the jacket?
You suspect she killed her grandson?
According to Brother Nam,
on the night Chung died,
Mother bought sugarcane from Wong Kee.
I wanted to ask Brother Nam about it,
but I found out something else.
(From Ko Cho Village to Wan Mei Village)
(Oct 15, Wan Mei Village)
I dared not ask Brother Nam directly.
I was worried he'd destroy the evidence.
I suspect Mother told Brother Nam
to drive her to Wan Mei Village
to kill Chung.
I think Mother is the prime suspect.
It's so sad how Chung died.
How is this Brother Nam related to you?
Tang Heung-nam is Mother's cousin.
He's also Chung's godfather.
He runs a coffin shop in Hunghom
and is also a Taoist priest.
He's well connected and has clout.
He almost has the monopoly on
all funerals in the walled villages
in the New Territories.
How is his relationship with Tang Suk-han?
Mother always trusted him.
When Father left everything to Chung,
I'm not sure if she was so angry,
she took Brother Nam with her to kill Chung.
Police! Can we have a word?
Sure!
What's your relationship with Tan Suk-han?
She's my cousin.
Kin-kwok and I hit it off well.
I took care of his funeral.
Do you know Cheung Kin-kwok didn't
leave anything to his wife?
Did they have a fight over anything?
Maybe he felt closer to Chung.
Then Cheung Wang-chi should be closer.
It's hard to say how people got along.
I'll cut to the chase.
Where were you the night
Cheung Siu-chung died?
I don't remember.
No? Mind if we look at your
navigation search log?
Check the night of October 15.
Did he search the route to Wan Mei Village?
It shows the route from Ko Cho Village
to Wan Mei Village.
We found out you and Tang Suk-han
bought sugarcane
and then went to Wan Mei Village.
Did you two kill Cheung Siu-chung?
Don't try to pin that on me.
Why were you there?
I ran into Cousin Han at the fruit store.
She wanted me to drive her to
Wan Mei Village.
I stayed in the car the whole time.
I didn't know what happened.
How did she know the address?
She got it from Tai-di's phone.
What time was that?
Around 11p.m., I really don't remember.
What did Tang Suk-han want
with Cheung Siu-chung?
Probably about the money.
She didn't tell me. I didn't ask.
Then I drove her home.
When she got back into the car,
what was her reaction?
She looked pissed and wanted to go home.
How would you describe her relationship
with Cheung Siu-chung?
She always doted on Chung.
But after she found out Kin-kwok
and her daughter-in-law had an affair...
Cheung Kin-kwok and Leung Yuet-ping?
I shouldn't have said that.
After that, she was angry with Chung.
Who else knows about this?
Everyone in the house.
But nobody in the village.
After Kin-kwok left everything to Chung,
Cousin Han suspected Chung's father
was someone else
and they were after the money.
The crazy thing was
Cousin Han thought it was me.
That was so unfair!
But in the end, Ping admitted it.
Chung was Kin-kwok's son.
Cousin Han was furious.
Cheung Siu-chung was Cheung Kin-kwok
and Leung Yuet-ping's son?!
That's why Kin-kwok left Chung everything.
It was better than giving it to Chi.
If you knew about this,
why didn't you tell the Police?
I only found out later Chung died
inside the village house.
I didn't want any trouble.
Cousin Han told me to keep my mouth shut.
This way, officers!
Grandma!
Ms. Tang Suk-han, this is a search warrant.
We have reasons to believe
you're hiding crucial evidence in
the murder of Cheung Siu-chung.
We need to search your room.
What crime have I committed?
Why do you want to search my room?
The Police have a search warrant
issued by the court.
They have the right to search the house.
Thank you.
Don't mess up my things.
What is it doing here?
Is this your jacket?
Yes...no! I threw it away.
I took it to the cleaner...
I don't remember.
Sze Sir, we found Cheung Siu-chung's watch.
What?
That's Chung's watch!
Why do you have it?
I thought the watch was lost.
Grandma, why didn't you tell us you had it?
You went to Wan Mei Village that night?
You wanted Chung to split the money.
He refused and you killed him in a rage!
After you found out the watch stopped
after midnight,
you were afraid you won't get
the inheritance,
that's why you hid the watch, am I right?
Don't go shooting off your mouth!
I don't know why the watch is in here.
Mom...I saw you throw away the watch.
I picked it up and put it back
in the drawer.
Ms. Tang Suk-han,
we suspect you're connected to a murder
in Wan Mei Village.
You're now under arrest.